Downloaded From MoviesMod.Org
[upbeat music playing]
[door opens]
Oh, hey.
Hi.
[Alex] Going for a run?
Yeah. You?
I'm just heading out for practice.
The tryouts for Blake's dad
are in a couple weeks,
and I really want that sponsorship.
-You'll do great.
-I wanted to talk to you.
Now that I passed my driver's test--
All right, no need to rub it in.
I don't know why you're so nervous.
You'll be fine.
Okay, thanks.
I was thinking.
I want us to go on a real date.
Yeah, okay. I guess.
But we'll have to go somewhere
where no one will see us.
The movies? We could go to Lockwood.
The Mirror Ball's showing horror classics.
Yeah, sounds good.
Okay, so I'll say I'm going to a party
with the rodeo guys.
And I'll say that I'm going to Grace's.
Hey.
-Hey.
What are you guys doin'?
-Nothing.
-I'm just going to practice.
Um… so the parallel parking is
at the end of the road test?
Yes, after all of the… driving.
-Got it.
-[Alex] Yeah.
-You're gonna ace it.
-Hope so.
[Alex chuckles]
Okay, well, guess I'll see you guys later.
See ya.
Beautiful out.
[Will] Okay, Dad,
what are we doing out here?
See this?
It's loam soil.
Is that a good thing?
Yeah, if you want to grow grapes.
Grapes?
-What's going on?
-Okay.
So apparently your dad's great-grandfather
made wine during Prohibition.
And we always knew there'd be grapes
somewhere, but we just didn't know where.
Until I found this vine. Look.
When I was out looking for Murphy.
This thing has survived
out here all that time.
I mean, this is the answer
to our financial problems, Will.
I thought the guest ranch
was our answer, Dad.
The guest ranch
was supposed to be me and you,
some yurts, and horseback riding.
And I blinked,
and there was a lodge in our front yard.
And… and Richard just taking
the whole thing over.
So I'll talk to him.
We'll scale it back to what it was.
It's too late, Will.
-I'm ending it.
-[Will] You can't do that.
We paid for the permits.
We've run the utility lines.
-There's a contract.
-I'm gonna go talk to Richard about that.
So you're just going to start a winery?
Do you have any idea how hard that is?
How long it takes to turn a profit?
Yeah, we do.
Which is why we're gonna lease
the land to Little Cap Winery.
The income's immediate, and we can
start to pay back our investors.
So… that's it?
Look, I know it's a pivot,
but this is going to be better.
For all of us.
[somber music playing]
So, have you thought
more about Día de los Muertos?
I know you didn't want
to do anything last year,
but I was thinking
maybe we could get together tomorrow
before I fly back to New York?
You're going back to New York?
Yeah, I have some meetings
about the ranch.
Is everything going okay now
with the ranch?
After the barn and everything?
You know these things aren't
without their hiccups along the way,
but it'll all work out.
-Yeah?
-Yeah.
Nothing for you to worry about, all right?
All right.
So… tomorrow?
I don't know.
Up to you. We can always do it next year.
Sure.
I feel bad about Will.
[horse whinnies]
He worked so hard.
I'll give it a minute
and then go talk to him.
I don't think Richard's
gonna take it much better.
Well, that one's not my problem.
Yeah, but, um…
he wanted to tell you this himself.
Oh boy. What?
He's in over his head financially.
He used his own money for this.
He said he had investors.
Why would he do that?
'Cause Jackie's
the only family he's got left.
[upbeat music playing]
Okay, that's ten volunteers for
the community garden clean up next week.
Then I think that's it for today.
Oh, Principal Whitmore asked us
to hang these posters up in school.
So maybe everyone can take a few posters
and hang them up on your way out.
I've seen these around town.
The Silver Falls Sparkle?
Yeah, it's pretty fun.
The whole town's
decorated in these twinkly lights.
There's food trucks and games and music.
Hot chocolate.
The church does a charity raffle.
Yeah, and there's an awards ceremony
for people that have done, like,
cool or special things
to contribute to the town in some way.
It's the most Silver Falls thing ever.
[Erin and Grace chuckle]
Great. What can we do to help?
Nothing. There's a town committee
that handles everything.
Okay, that's it. See you guys next week,
and happy Halloween.
-[Grace] Yeah.
-[Skylar] Ooh.
Thanks, Erin.
[Grace] So, I was thinking about tonight.
The house on Rogers Street
always goes all out as a haunted house.
And I've never been 'cause my parents.
Plus, it does look really scary.
But I was thinking if we go together,
it could be kind of fun.
Actually, Alex and I are going on a date.
Oh.
So I was hoping
I could say I was with you.
Uh, sure. Yeah. I love being
a cover story for a secret rendezvous.
-Thanks.
-Where are you guys going?
Okay. So what are we doing
for Halloween tonight?
Uh, nothing.
Nothing. I gotta study
for the math test next week.
Got a D on the last one
and my dad hit the roof.
So, uh, yeah, Jackie's gonna come over
and help me study.
Right, Jackie?
Oh, right.
I think I want to have
a Halloween party tonight.
Do you really feel up to throwing a party
after the whole Zach and Nathan thing?
Honestly, I'm hoping
it'll make me feel better.
Right. Well, Halloween's in six hours.
And six hours isn't enough time
to put together a whole party.
It doesn't have to be fancy.
There's this space above Monty's.
It's kinda creepy. We could do it there.
Grace, you can spread the word around
the whole school before last period.
Uh, yeah, I guess.
But what about food, decorations, drinks?
Jackie, come on.
I need this.
After Nathan.
Okay.
-Yay! [laughs]
-I'll help.
[Grace squeals]
Alex, wanna come to our Halloween party?
-Tonight?
-[Skylar] Yeah, it's Halloween.
We can't. We're on little-kid duty
for trick-or-treating. Remember?
I thought you just said
you were studying with Grace?
Uh…
[spluttering]
Yeah, that's after.
So come to the party instead.
Okay, sure. Yeah, see you there.
-Happy Halloween!
-[Skylar chuckles]
-I'll see y'all tonight, okay?
-Okay.
-What was that about?
-Oh, Skylar's having a Halloween party.
Guess I'm not invited, huh?
I'll stay home with you.
You're still not talking to Erin?
I don't think she's talking to me.
Scary movie night it is.
[overlapping chatter]
Okay, everybody! Listen up! Listen up.
I was in high school once.
So I understand
the pressures to partake in drugs
and alcohol.
But as student athletes, we need
to hold ourselves to higher standards.
And sadly, some of you are not doing that.
The following players
had positive drug tests
and will be suspended from the team
until further notice.
[player] Seriously?
Carter Reeves, Sean Stanley,
and Dylan Newsome.
Isaac.
-You're our new quarterback.
-[player 2] No, what?!
[overlapping chatter]
Dylan, hey, wait up.
What do you want?
-Are you okay?
-No, I'm not.
Because of you, I'm benched.
No way we'll make playoffs.
Wait. It's not my fault
you failed your drug test.
But you got exactly what you wanted.
Your cousin is quarterback,
and you don't have to watch me
outshine you.
Are you serious?
I've been trying to help you.
Help? [scoffs]
You pushed me so hard,
I almost got injured.
I pushed you so that you'd play better,
so that we'd win.
-That's what a good coach does.
-No, you know what you should've done?
Taken the test for me.
But you didn't because you've been on
a mission to sabotage me since day one.
Is that what you think?
We just got a clean slate.
Why would I risk that after everything?
No one would've found out.
[scoffs] It's always
someone else's fault, isn't it?
And sabotage?
You don't need me for that.
Doing a great job on your own.
Okay. [clears throat]
Do you accelerate or decelerate
when exiting a freeway ramp?
-Decelerate.
-Perfect.
What do you do if your view
is blocked at a crosswalk?
Move forward carefully and look both ways
before slowly entering the intersection.
[Alex] Perfect.
Hey. I got our tickets
for the movie tonight.
Great.
So we'll just have to stop by
Skylar's party first.
I'll be there early to set up.
Then we'll need to leave separately
so that no one will suspect--
-Right.
You know, maybe one of these days
we can actually go to a party together.
Yeah, of course.
I just think
that with everything going on,
now's not the best time to tell anyone.
Don't you?
Yeah, sure.
No.
What is it?
I…
I just… it's almost gone.
Can't you just get another bottle?
No. And that's not the point.
It was my mom's.
Oh.
I'm sorry. I--
It's okay. It's just perfume.
It's fine. I'll be fine.
Um…
But I… I better go.
Okay. You're gonna do great.
Thanks.
[sighs]
How the hell did Garcia
even make second string?
Dude, he overthrows me every time.
[Jay] Yo, Cole.
I know he's your cousin and all,
but he can't hit a target
to save his life.
Right. I forgot you guys
were perfect on your first day.
Give him a break.
Ready to begin?
Ready.
The orange cones represent other vehicles
for you to maneuver around.
Be very mindful of those
as you reverse out of the parking space.
Got it.
All right, back out past the last cone,
then exit the parking lot that way.
Sorry, these brakes are
a little more sensitive than I'm used to.
Hey! Put the vehicle in park.
Can I try again?
You knocked over two cones.
-But I… I didn't even--
-That's a fail.
[sighs]
All right, so I'm taking
the kids out trick-or-treating,
so I need you two to man the door, please.
Why do we bother? Trick-or-treaters
never come all the way here.
Hey, this could be the year.
Can we get a pizza?
[sighs]
-Sure.
-Yes!
Oh, you made it back in one piece!
[clears throat]
-I failed.
-[George] Oh, sorry.
But hey, listen, it's no big deal
because he failed three times.
Okay, yeah, but in my defense,
I had a cold the second time,
so it doesn't count.
You know, I think Alex is the only one
who didn't fail it on his first time, so
you're really just keeping up
with the family tradition.
I'm sure you'll ace the next one.
-Unless you get a cold.
-[chuckles]
Thanks. I should get ready.
Grace is picking me up
to take me to the party, so…
Really? It was a cold?
-Can you stop with the cold? Stop it.
-It was!
♪ We doing Halloween ♪
♪ Like you ain't ever seen… ♪
[creepy laughing]
Guys, we transformed this place into
Hullapalooza in less than three hours.
That's a record. Even for us.
Oh my God, you're kidding me.
What? Cute costume.
I mean, gothic princess vibes?
It's not a gothic princess.
That's La Calavera Catrina.
La Cala what?
Just some mild cultural appropriation.
Oh.
-Do you want me to go uninvite her?
-No, it's fine. I'm fine.
Okay.
♪ Don't let your freak out ♪
♪ Don't let the freak out… ♪
[Alex] Hey, nice costume.
Thanks. You too.
Thanks.
And you didn't dress up?
What are you talking about?
I'm… I'm James Dean.
Who's James Dean?
-[Richard] George.
-[George] Hey.
Shouldn't you be trick-or-treating?
Well, kids were already home
with enough candy to get 'em to Easter.
[chuckles]
And I collected my dad tax, of course.
Want some?
Sounds like a successful night.
Yeah.
-Would you like to come in for a drink?
-Sure.
So, what's so important
you had to come over?
Well, the guest ranch.
Well, I gathered that.
-Thank you.
-[Richard] Mm-hmm.
Look.
I know how much you…
have personally invested in this.
[Richard] Mmm.
So Katherine told you?
Look, Richard, you really saved us
when we needed it, and I appreciate that.
But I'm officially pulling the plug
on the project.
[Richard chuckles]
It's a little late for that.
We have a contract.
Legally, you can't stop us.
Well, I'm not so sure.
You know, as I said before, the contract
doesn't say anything
about a development this size.
Two of my fraternity brothers
are real estate attorneys.
-Are you sure you want to do this?
-Look.
You told my wife that the whole reason
you did this was because Jackie's family.
Yeah, and to save your ass.
[George] And I'm grateful.
Can we just not do the lawyer thing?
If Jackie's your family, then we are too.
No, calling me family
isn't gonna change the fact
that you are screwing me over
and that you owe me money.
[George] I agree, so hear me out.
[sighs]
Look, I have a plan for the land
that will get you every dime
of your money back, plus interest.
Almost immediately.
Okay, I'm listening.
♪ You light me up inside ♪
♪ You make me come alive ♪
♪ You know you give me
light, light, light, light ♪
♪ Like a solar flare ♪
♪ Can't get no hotter ♪
♪ I'm ablaze for you tonight… ♪
Hey, boys.
Selfie?
♪ Let's take it higher… ♪
Thanks for coming out tonight.
♪ So take it higher ♪
-♪ So take it higher ♪
-♪ Take it higher ♪
♪ So take it higher
♪ Across the sky ♪
♪ Hot ♪
♪ I always got you back ♪
♪ I always got your heart ♪
♪ We go back and forth ♪
♪ Somehow we never fall apart ♪
♪ Loved you more than once ♪
♪ Loved you more than twice… ♪
-Of course you didn't dress up.
-Hey, I came straight from work.
But I did make an effort.
Mmm. Nice. [chuckles]
I heard about the suspension.
How are you doing?
Honestly?
I'm fine.
♪ I'm running back to you, yeah… ♪
Hey, Jimmy.
[Cole] Seriously?
You're still on this?
♪ Let's be on our way… ♪
You know what?
I'm out.
♪ Jumping in the lake… ♪
What was that all about?
Him not having my back.
What do you mean?
He could've made
this whole thing not happen.
How? It's not like
he could've done anything.
♪ I'm calling out to you, yeah ♪
♪ I want a piece of your… ♪
Wait.
Did you ask Cole
to take the drug test for you?
♪ I'm running back to you, yeah… ♪
Look, it doesn't matter.
My dad made a donation
to the athletic department.
He wasn't about to let me
miss the showcase.
And well, this school lives for State,
so… back on the team
starting Monday. [chuckles]
So Daddy just came in with his checkbook
and made all your troubles disappear?
And that's, uh, a problem because?
Because how come you don't have to play
by the rules like the rest of us?
Come on, Kiley. It's not that simple.
Wow.
It must be nice to not have to be
held accountable for anything.
♪ You flick a switch, don't you know? ♪
I'll see you later.
♪ I'm calling out to you… ♪
Wait, K… Kiley!
-♪ I wanna piece of your sunshine, baby… ♪
-[sighs] Great.
♪ Yeah, I'm running back to you
I'm running-- ♪
-[scary music on TV]
-[howling on TV]
♪ When I step in the room
I'm the best dressed ♪
♪ Textin'
Add another body to my excellence ♪
♪ Blowin' up my phone
If it ain't about the money… ♪
-[boy] Want a shot?
-I'm good, thanks.
♪ Come, come, come through
With the check, right? ♪
♪ Lookin' at the trip
Throw a hop on the next slide ♪
♪ Everybody knows
Rock boys don't deserve no cake ♪
♪ I don't really wanna argue
Get the poop out my face… ♪
Hey, I'll see you guys later.
-[boy] All right.
-[boy 2] Yeah. See you, dude.
♪ Livin' like a movie, just sayin' ♪
♪ You gonna live this way
But you miss the ride ♪
♪ I betcha feelin' like you're growin' ♪
♪ We gettin' to it over here… ♪
Um, I gotta go.
♪ We gettin' to it ♪
♪ Why you cappin'? ♪
♪ By the way, if we're movin'… ♪
[Alex] Hey.
Hey.
You wanna… get out of here?
-Yeah.
-[Alex] Do you have all your stuff?
[phone buzzing]
Give me one second.
What? [groans]
-What's wrong?
-It's Kiley. She needs my help.
Oh.
Uh, okay. Yeah, go.
-We'll see the movie another time.
-Are you sure?
Of course. It's fine. I'm fine.
Okay. See you.
♪ But you miss the ride
I betcha feelin' like you're growin' ♪
♪ We gettin' to it over here
We gettin' to it ♪
♪ We gettin' to it over here… ♪
Okay. What's going on between you two?
-What do you mean?
-You and Alex.
-You're back on?
-No, what?
Um…
What makes you think that?
I'm not stupid.
Jackie, who you date is up to you.
And I like Alex.
He's always seemed like a super sweet guy,
and he's definitely gotten hotter
over the past few months.
♪ We gettin' to it over here
We gettin' to it… ♪
But?
♪ Just sayin' ♪
♪ You're gonna live this way… ♪
Part of me always thought
maybe you and Cole.
What? No.
No, we're just friends.
Okay.
♪ You never do it ♪
-[new song starts]
-♪ Good thing going ♪
♪ Got a good thing going… ♪
Look, I know why Danny and I
kept our relationship hidden at first,
but why are you keeping yours a secret?
I mean, you like Alex, right?
Yeah, I do.
It's complicated.
You won't say anything, will you?
No, of course not.
And you don't have to listen to me.
Danny and I were fine until we weren't.
So maybe you're right
to keep things to yourselves.
It's no one else's business anyway.
[sighs]
Erin, I don't know
what happened with you and Danny,
but I do know that he wouldn't do anything
to deliberately hurt you.
Yeah, I…
I think I know that. It's just…
Like you said, it's complicated.
♪ Just gotta keep on going
Till I reach that holy ground ♪
Okay, come on.
Come on, let's go inside. Grams.
Hey.
-What's wrong with her?
-She just gets like this sometimes.
Has she been drinking?
She's okay, I just…
I need help getting her inside.
Okay. Okay.
[rock music playing]
God, I mean,
there are no hot single guys here.
This party sucks.
Yeah. I thought having a party
would take my mind off things,
but honestly, it's just making it worse.
Although, I can now confirm,
Billy Edwards,
not 100% straight.
What?
-You're crazy.
-[boy] Hey, Skylar.
-Someone's throwing up in the bathroom.
-Ugh.
Gotta go.
[Grace] Why are you still here?
Shouldn't you be at the movies with Alex?
He had to leave.
It is literally impossible
for Alex and I to find alone time,
and so tonight, we were going
to actually have a normal date.
But no, of course not.
I have to get roped into
organizing a party.
And then Alex leaves, and on top of that,
I failed my driver's test
before I even got out of the parking lot.
The parking lot, Grace.
Who does that? Not Jackie Howard.
Jackie Howard has
never failed a test until today.
Okay, tomorrow will be better.
Tomorrow is worse.
Tomorrow is the Day of the…
-Oh no, you don't.
-Wait.
Hey, hey, where are you going?
-To rip that outfit off that stupid--
-Whoa. What outfit?
That's La Calavera Catrina.
And I bet that she has no idea
who that is or what that even means.
-So?
-So she shouldn't be wearing it.
Okay, okay, hey. Settle down.
Look at me. Look at me.
Breathe.
[exhales]
You okay?
Fine.
-Are you sure we shouldn't call 911?
-[Kiley] No.
No, she doesn't need a doctor.
She needs to sleep it off.
This happens all the time.
She'll be fine in the morning.
[Alex] I had no idea, Kyles.
Why didn't you tell me?
We haven't really been talking much.
Um… well, you gotta tell someone.
-Like who?
-I don't know. A teacher or something.
If I tell a teacher or a doctor,
they'll call Child Protective Services.
And then what?
-What do you think would happen to me?
-I don't know.
Foster care, Alex.
-I'm not doing that.
-Kiley.
Your grandma's the adult.
She should be taking care of you.
Yes, you're right.
She should.
But not everybody gets a perfect family.
[somber music playing]
[Cole] Hey. Hey.
Is this about the driving test?
Because Will failed his first time out.
-So did I. And Danny, he--
-Failed three times.
I know!
Wait, how did you know I didn't pass?
Well, there's no secrets
in the Walter household. So…
If it's not the test, then
what is it?
I know it sounds stupid,
but it's about tomorrow.
Tomorrow?
Día de los Muertos.
It means something, you know?
It's not just a costume.
It's supposed to be a celebration
for those who have died.
And I just… I can't do it.
-Don't beat yourself up.
-What is wrong with me?
-Why can't I celebrate my family?
-There is nothing wrong with you.
And there's still time,
if you want to do it.
Tomorrow
is about keeping their memories alive.
But they're fading.
And when I'm in New York
and I'm surrounded by the places we went
or the things we did together,
they feel… they feel closer.
You know, it feels more real.
But they were never here in Silver Falls,
so it's like
there's nothing of them to hold onto.
And the more that I try to fit in here,
the further it feels like I am from them.
I think… I think I'm losing them, Cole.
And I… I'm kinda…
I'm kind losing myself too.
No, you're… you're not losing yourself.
Hey.
You will always be a Howard.
And to me…
you'll always be New York.
Okay?
Hey.
Yeah.
Let's get you home.
Okay.
[Kiley] Thank you.
For coming.
Nah, you can always call me.
Can you not tell anyone… about this?
Course not.
So is this why you've been,
like, off lately?
Me?
Alex,
since you came back from rodeo school,
you haven't had room for me.
Yeah, because you've made it pretty clear
you don't want to be around me anymore.
You just seem mad at me all the time.
I'm not mad at you.
Then what is it?
At Will and Haley's wedding…
you said I was practically a dude.
Ah.
Did I?
Mm-hmm.
Ah.
I just meant that you're, like,
really cool and easy to be around.
Come on. Kiley.
I've missed you.
I've missed you too.
Kyles?
Yeah?
We okay?
Sure.
We're okay.
[man on TV] Imagine for one moment
the complexity of the human brain.
The same size, perhaps,
but a million times more efficient.
You are just in time
for part two of our double feature.
[Cole] Think I have a better idea.
Candy poker?
-Who's in?
-I'm in.
-Yep.
-[Cole] Yes.
-[Nathan] All right, who's gonna deal?
-[Danny] I can deal.
[Nathan] All right, Danny,
but you better mix 'em up right.
[Danny] Yeah, I will.
New York? You want to play?
I warn you, we're ruthless.
And take all of your candy?
Are you sure?
Oh, she's a hustler.
Okay. Let's see what you got.
Challenge accepted.
Guys, come on. Let's play.
Okay. Here we go.
All right.
[Richard sighs]
[Jackie] It's beautiful.
Do you want to say something or should I?
You go ahead.
To the spirits of those we loved,
welcome on this special day.
We honor and celebrate your lives.
The love we shared with you,
we will carry with us forever.
Feliz Día de los Muertos.
And, um,
I wanted to show you something.
What is it?
[woman] Okay, here we go.
[Jackie] Oh my God.
-It's my fifth birthday party.
-[Richard] Mm-hmm.
Happy birthday, mi amor.
Here you go.
Make a wish.
Bravo!
Good job.
Where did you get this?
[Richard] I recorded it
all those years ago.
[woman] Hope it doesn't come true.
I haven't been able
to bring myself to watch it.
Until today.
-Today's the perfect time.
-Yeah.
Well, there's plenty more
where this came from.
-Really?
-[Richard] Mm-hmm.
I was hoping we could make a day of it.
If you want to. At least until
I have to leave for the airport.
[sniffles]
-I'd love that.
-Good. Come on.
[door opens]
-Want me to quiz you?
-I know the plays.
Green right, 23 Z-zap on two.
"Z-zap" tells the receiver to run a zap
motion parallel to the line of scrimmage.
Snap's on the second hut.
Don't know what happened
in practice yesterday.
I've been watching Dylan all season.
Well, you just gotta shake off the nerves.
No, I'm not nervous. It's just that…
You know?
Hey.
First time Coach put me in,
I was so freaked out,
I puked in the huddle.
All over the senior running back's cleats.
-Really?
-Mm-hmm.
-Damn.
-[Cole chuckles]
So, you'll be fine. Just… don't puke.
Don't puke. Got it.
[chuckles]
[scoffs]
A lot to learn, though.
[mellow rock music playing]
[knock on door]
Son, how you doing?
[music fades]
Have you, um, spoken with Richard?
-No.
-I have.
I know you're disappointed.
I know how hard you worked.
I just wanna tell you
how proud I am of you,
despite how this turned out.
[scoffs]
You're still shutting it down.
It just wasn't right for us, Will.
-And it would've torn the family apart.
-No, I wouldn't have let that happen.
It already was happening.
You were putting what Richard wanted
ahead of what your mom and I wanted.
I had asked you guys to shut it down twice
and you just kept working.
Because that's what we agreed to.
[sighs] Look, we found a better solution.
Right? And Richard gets that.
Will, I want you to be involved.
[scoffs]
Dad, you're leasing the land.
You get a check. They do the work.
There isn't anything
for me to be involved with.
What am I gonna do, just sit and watch?
[Richard] I gotta get to my flight,
but I'll be back in a couple days.
Say hi to the city for me.
Will do.
Thanks again for today.
I'm really glad we did this.
They were with us. I have no doubt.
Well, uh, stay as long as you want.
Here's a key
in case you need
some alone time while I'm gone.
I know it can get crowded at the Walters'.
I'll water your plants.
Okay.
-I love you.
-[Jackie] Love you.
-Bye-bye.
-Bye.
[gentle upbeat playing]
Hey.
They post 'em yet?
Yep.
Look, um, SATs don't mean everything.
There's still so many places
you could apply.
I got a 1250.
What?
Cole, that's incredible.
-All right, calm down.
-Come on!
-Come here!
-Calm down.
I got a 1250.
Yeah!
[gentle music playing]
♪ Crying eyes, broken bells ♪
♪ Back in course… ♪
So, what happened with Kiley last night?
Nothing. It was her grandma.
They were moving a sofa,
and she hurt her ankle.
-Is she okay?
-Oh, yeah.
-How was the rest of the party?
-It was kind of boring.
-I didn't stay long.
-Mmm.
-Sounds like I didn't miss much.
-No.
But I missed you.
♪ Your love is always waking mine ♪
♪ I wanna break down
Where your heart gets so torn ♪
♪ It's almost breaking mine ♪
♪ I wanna lay here ♪
♪ Lost and bitter ♪
♪ So long I feel like I could die ♪
♪ I wanna tell you what my truth is ♪
♪ But it's buried down inside ♪
♪ Oh, I had a dream ♪
♪ That you couldn't hear me screaming ♪
♪ Tried to tell you everything ♪
♪ But it wouldn't stop you leaving ♪
♪ I wanna wake up where your love is ♪
♪ 'Cause your love is always waking mine ♪
♪ I wanna break down ♪
♪ Where your heart gets so torn ♪
♪ It's almost breaking mine ♪
♪ I wanna lay here lost and bitter ♪
♪ So long I feel like I could die ♪
♪ I wanna tell you what my truth is ♪
♪ But it's buried down inside ♪
♪ They say that secrets make you sick
And I should know ♪
♪ Just promise me that if I tell you ♪
♪ You will go ♪
♪ It's buried down inside ♪
Downloaded From MoviesMod.Org